女士们  先生们  请系好您的安全带
Ladies and gentlemen,  please fasten your seatbelts.
正常情况
It's normal.
前集提要
Previously on  Lost...
在那别动
Stay there!
宫缩了
I'm having contractions.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
有时间的话能帮我个忙吗
Do you have a second? I could use a little help here.
我本来可以自己来的
Look,  I'd do it myself,
我是个医生  可够不到...
I'm a doctor, but I just can't reach...
你想让我缝那伤口吗
You want me to sew that up?
你看起来一点儿也不害怕
You don't seem afraid at all.
我不明白
I don't understand that.
他们知道我们在哪儿
They know exactly where we are.
他们会来的
They're coming.
你以为他们现在就该到了
You'd think they would have come by now.
看见了吗
Did anybody see that?
可怕极了
Terrific.
我要去找驾驶舱了
I'm gonna go out and look for the cockpit.
看是否能找到无线电收发机
See if we can find a transceiver
发射求救信号
to send a distress signal.
Kate  告诉我烟从哪来
Kate, you showed me where the smoke was.
我自己去
I can get there myself.
我要去
I'm coming.
伙计们  这算是正常吗
Hey, guys, is this normal?
白天变成了黑夜
Day turning into night,
世界末日一样的天气  伙计们
You know, end of the world-type weather? Is this...guys?
偏离了航线一千英里
We were 1,000 miles off course.
他们搜救我们找错地方了
They're looking for us in the wrong place.
你在洗手间里做什么
What were you doing in the bathroom?
是什么鬼东西
What the hell was that?
刚才发生了什么事
What the hell just happened?
Jack
Jack!
这是怎么搞的
How does something like that happen?
今晚...
他们的故事将继续...
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：ljw1911  雯雯  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
有声吗
Anything?
你问个不停
You keep asking if there's anything.
原谅我所表露出的绝望
Pardon me for appearing desperate,
但在机长被拽出驾驶舱之前
but before the pilot was ripped from the cockpit,
他确实说了没有人会找到我们
he did say that no one's gonna find us
除非我们能把无线电收发机修好
unless we get that transceiver working.
所以
So...
有声吗
Is there anything?
好吧
Okay.
你当时在洗手间里做什么
So what were you doing in the bathroom?
我以为你知道
Thought you could tell.
我恶心了
I was getting sick.
在吐
Puking.
我对这次艰苦跋涉所做出的杰出贡献
My one tangible contribution to the trek.
不  我很高兴你来了  Charlie
No, I'm glad you came, Charlie.
每个旅行都需要一个懦夫
Every trek needs a coward.
你可不是懦夫
You're not a coward.
你没事吧  先生
Are you all right, sir?
没事
I'm good.
谢了
Thanks.
用我给你拿些水吗?
Can I get you a water?
没事  谢谢了
I'm fine. Thank you.
请吧
Please?
好
All right.
借过
Excuse me.
先生  等等
Sir? Excuse me!
Sir, excuse me.
看着点儿
Excuse me.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentleman,
机长已经打开了"安全带"指示灯
the captain has turned on the "fasten seatbelts" sign.
请返回您的座位并系好安全带
Please return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
先生  您没事吧
Sir? Are you all right?
等一下
Just a minute.
请您开门
I'm gonna have to ask that you open the door.
快开门  先生
Open the door now, sir.
先生
Sir?
我在检查衣服  整理一下
Hey. We're going through some clothes. Sorting them.
我看能否找到你的箱子
I see you found your bag.
来吧  想帮我一下吗
Come on, you wanna give us a hand?
不太想
Not really.
你在浪费时间  他们快到了
You're wasting your time. They're coming.
你男友吗
Is that your boyfriend?
我哥  Boone
My brother. Boone.
上帝赐予人类的讨厌鬼
God's friggin' gift to humanity.
我以前也有小腹的
I used to have a stomach.
知道性别吗
Do you know what it is?
还不知道
Not yet.
从昨天起我就感受不到胎儿在动了
I haven't felt the baby move since yesterday.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
看到我孩子了吗
Have you seen my boy?
抱歉
Sorry.
Walt! Walt!
Vincent!
来这里  小伙子
Come here, boy.
出了这么多事  我是怎么和你说的
What did I tell you after what's happened?
我以为Vincent会在这附近
I thought Vincent would be around.
我说过让你在沙滩上呆着
Stay on the beach.
这离沙滩很近  我以为没事呢
I thought this would be okay.
别顶嘴
Don't do that.
听我的话  我是认真的  知道吗
You listen to me, I mean what I say. You understand?
这是什么
What is this?
刚看到的
I just found 'em.
来
Come here.
伙计们  别打了
Hey, guys, come on.
停手吧
Hey! Break it up!
停手  算了
Break it up! Get off!
停手 够了 别打了  够了
Break up! That's it! It's over! That's it!
我烦死这乡巴佬了
I'm sick of this redneck!
还要来试试吗  小子
Want some more?
告诉大家你和我说什么来着
Tell everyone what you told me!
告诉他们是我使飞机坠毁的  说啊
Tell them that I crashed the plane! Go on!
就是你干的  老兄
The shoe fits!
怎么回事
What is going on?
我孩子在丛林里发现了这个
My kid found these in the jungle.
这家伙坐在飞机商务舱中的后排
This guy was in the back row of business class the whole flight.
从没起来过  手一直放在毯子底下
Never got up.Hands folded underneath the blanket.
不知什么原因  要说明的是
And for some reason, just pointing this out,
在他边上的那人却没活着
The guy next to him didn't make it.
非常感谢你观察我的一举一动
Thank you for observing.
你以为我没看到在登机前他们把你拽出去了吗
Don't think I saw them pull you out of line before we boarded?
过来  来啊
Come on! Bring it!
停手吧
Stop!
我们找到了无线电收发机  但不好用了
We found the transceiver, but it's not working.
有人会修吗
Can anybody help?
恩
Yes
我也许能帮上忙
I might be able to.
好嘛  好极了
Oh, great! Perfect.
相信他吧
Let's trust this guy.
我们都被困在了这里  哥们儿
Hey, we're all in this together.
互相尊重点好吗
Treat each other with respect...
闭嘴  猪头
Shut up, lardo.
省省吧
Give it a break.
随你的便  医生
Whatever you say, doc,
你是英雄
You're the hero.
你们找到了驾驶舱吗
You guys found the cockpit?
有幸存者吗
Any survivors?
没有
No.
是双带  军用规格的
Dual-band. Military spec.
现在的情况是还有电池
Chances are the battery is good,
但无线电坏了
but the radio is dead.
能修好吗
Can you fix it?
需要些时间
I need some time.
医生  带着碎片的那个人
Doctor, that man with the shrapnel,
我想你该去看看他
I think you should take a look at him.
二百五的烟鬼
Chain-smoking jackass.
有些人有毛病
Some people have problems.
恩  有些人和我们过不去
Some people have problems. Us.
他
Him.
你不错
You're okay.
我喜欢你
I like you.
你也不错
You're okay too.
Hurley.
Sayid.
你怎么会修这东西的
How do you know how to do that?
我以前是军事通讯员
I was a communications officer.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
你看过打仗吗
You ever see battle?
我打过海湾战争
I fought in the Gulf War.
不是吧  我有个兄弟就参加过
No way. I got a buddy who fought over there.
他以前在104空降团
He was in the 104th Airborne.
你呢  空军  陆军
What were you, Air Force? Army?
共和国卫队
The Republican Guard.
好用了吗
Is it working?
看来行了
It seems to be,
就差找到信号了
except we're not picking up a signal.
为什么要找信号呢
Why do we need to pick up a signal?
我们不是要发射信号吗
Aren't we trying to send one?
是的  但要看到小格
Yes, but what you want to see here is little bars.
信号格表示无线电被接收了
The bars show it's getting reception.
我们需要信号格
We need the bars?
我们可以盲播
We could broadcast blind,
希望有人或船能收到我们的求救信号
hope that someone, maybe a ship somewhere picks up our distress call.
但那样可能是在浪费电池
But that would be a waste of the battery,
电池可不多了
which might not last for long.
我们还可以试一个办法
There is one thing we could try.
看我们是否能从高地收到信号
Get the signal from high ground.
要多高
How high?
他怎么样了
How is he?
有什么办法吗
Can you do anything?
拔出碎片
I can pull out the shrapnel.
可你昨天说如果要拔了出来--
But you said if you took it out...
我知道  但那是昨天
That was yesterday.
我以为他现在该在医院了
I was hoping he'd be at a hospital by now.
如果再这样下去  他一天内就会死的
If I leave him like this he'll be dead within a day.
如果拔下来  然后止住血
If I open him up...If I can control the bleeding,
如果不化脓
and if he doesn't go into sepsis,
如果再能找到些抗生素
and if I can find some antibiotics,
他也许就会没事
he might be all right.
我要上山了
I'm going on a hike.
什么
Sorry?
Sayid修好了收发机  但用不了
SSayid fixed the transceiver, but we can't use it.
在这里用不了
Not from here.
Kate 等一下
Kate, wait a minute.
是你说我们必须要发射信号的
You said we had to send a signal.
你看到了那东西把机长弄成了什么样
Look, you saw what that thing did to that pilot.
恩  看到了
Yeah, I did.
为什么你认为我们在这里就比在丛林里安全呢
What makes you think we're any safer here than we are in the jungle?
等我  我不知道还要多久...
Wait for me. I don't know how long...
Sayid说电池不多了
Sayid said the battery won't last.
如果看到或听到什么东西
If you see or hear anything...
任何东西
Anything...
跑就是了
Run.
什么  那个
What, that?
什么  吃那个吗
What, eat that?
老兄  老兄
Dude, dude,
我是饿了
I'm starving.
可还不至于那么饿
But I am nowhere near that hungry.
不  不  谢谢了
No. No. No, thank you.
不吃  不了
No way. No.
是西班牙语漫画
The comic's in Spanish. You...
你懂西班牙语
...read Spanish?
不懂
No.
我找到的
I found it.
告诉你吧  我们回家后
Tell you what, we get home...
我再给你弄一条狗
...l'll get you another dog.
要你帮下忙
I need your help.
好
Okay.
帮我查看一下行李
Help me go through the luggage.
我需要各种处方药和药品
I need any prescription medications you find,
特别是以"素"和"西林"为结尾的药
especially drugs that end in "mycin" and "cillin."
那些是抗生素
Those are antibiotics.
用来干什么
What's this for?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我想我对他太凶了
I think I was mean to him.
他是那个在门口的人
He's that guy from the gate.
不让我们坐我们头等舱座位的人
He wouldn't let us have our seats in first class.
他救了我们
He saved our lives.
来吧  Shannon 我们要清理些残骸
Shannon, we're trying to clear the wreckage.
你该帮帮忙
You should help out.
你在这儿无所事事的
You're just being worthless over here.
我什么
I'm being what?
你想让我怎么说
What do you want me to say?
你坐在那儿盯着尸体
You're sitting on your ass staring at bodies.
我刚遭受了打击  知道吗
I've just been through a trauma here, okay?
我们都遭受了打击
We've all been through a trauma.
唯一区别就是  自从失事以来
The only difference is, since the crash,
你一直在进行所谓的治疗
you've actually given yourself a pedicure.
你知道什么  那么容易就可以取笑我  你还乐此不疲
You know what? It is so easy to make fun of me, and you're good at it.
我倒希望不用浪费我的时间来...
I wish I didn't have to waste ly time...
我希望没有理由  是的  很容易  Shannon
I wish I didn't have a reason. Yeah, it is easy, Shannon.
去你的  你根本就不知道我的想法
Screw you. You do not have the slightest idea what I am thinking.
我要比你清楚的多
I have a much better idea than you think I do.
不  不是
No, you don't!
好  Shannon 那你想干什么
Okay, Shannon, what are you thinking?
我要和他们一起去登山
I'm going with them on the hike.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
对  我这就去
Yup. I'm going.
不  不行  Shannon
No you're not, Shannon.
Shannon!
我要和你们一起去
I'd like to come with you.
她不去
She's not going.
才不是
The hell I'm not!
她的糟糕决定让她的家人不快
She postures and makes really bad decisions to upset her family
而此时那家人就是我
which, at the moment, is me.
闭嘴  别耍帅了
Shut up and stop trying to be charming.
我和你们一起去
I'm coming with you.
这不太好吧
I don't know if that's a good idea.
你怎么回事  就比我大两岁  拜托
What are you, two years older than me? Please?
你要去  是吧
You're going, aren't you?
恩  你呢
Yeah. Are you?
恩
Yup.
那我去定了
Yeah, I'm definitely going.
谁都可以来  可现在就要出发了
Look, everybody can come. But we're leaving now.
别对她妄下断言  她人不错的
You couldn't tell from that, but she's really nice.
你决定了加入我们
You decided to join us.
我性情不定  甜心
I'm a complex guy, sweetheart.
在找什么
What are you looking for?
刀片什么的
Some sort of blade.
你儿子怎么样了
How's your son?
Walt吗  恩  我想他会没事的
Walt? Yeah, I think he'll be all right.
他多大了
How old is he?
九岁  十岁
Nine. Ten.
十岁
Ten.
Walt最担心的就是他的狗了
Walt's more worried about his dog than anything.
狗在飞机上  所以...
The dog was on the plane, so...
小孩子  这你也知道
Kids, you know.
拉布拉多尔狗吗
Is it a lab?
恩
Yeah.
是吧
Yeah?
昨天在丛林里看到过
I saw him yesterday in the jungle.
什么
What?
哪儿
Where?
那边
Over there...
大约几百码吧
A couple hundred yards in or so.
看起来还不错
He looked good.
是什么东西  这和跳棋一样吗
What is it, like checkers?
不太一样  这比跳棋更有趣
Not really. It's a better game than checkers.
你和你老爸玩跳棋吗
Do you play checkers with your pop?
没有
No.
我和妈妈住在澳大利亚
I live in Australia with my mom.
你没有那的口音
You have no accent.
恩  我们常搬家
Yeah, I know, we move a lot.
她生病了
She got sick.
几周前死了
She died a couple of weeks ago.
你这个月不顺哪
You're having a bad month.
我想是吧
I guess.
双陆棋是世界上最古老的游戏了
Backgammon is the oldest game in the world.
考古学家在挖掘美索不达米亚古代遗迹的时候
Archaeologists found sets when they excavated the ruins
就找到了很多套
of ancient Mesopotamia.
五千年前就有了
Five thousand years old.
比耶稣基督还要久远
That's older than Jesus Christ.
他们有骰子什么的吗
Did they have dice and stuff?
恩  但不是用塑料做的
But theirs weren't made of plastic.
他们的骰子是用骨头做的
Their dice were made of bones.
酷
Cool.
两名选手  两方
Two players. Two sides.
一白  一黑
One is light. One is dark.
Walt
Walt...
想知道一个秘密吗
...do you wanna know a secret?
不  多谢
No, thank you.
不  没关系
No, that's fine.
好  谢了
Okay. Thanks.
天哪
Oh, God.
我感觉到了
I just felt it!
来  摸一下  摸一下
I just... Come here, feel this!
感觉到了吗
Do you feel that?
看  踢了
That, right there.That's a kick!
就这儿  脚在这儿
There, right there's a foot!
等一下  他在动
Oh, my God, wait,he's moving around.
他  他
He. He.
我想你是个男孩子
I guess I think you're a he.
好了  开阔地带
Okay. Wide open space.
你该试一下无线电  看看好用不
Check the radio, see if we're good.
在这里不会收到的
We're not gonna have reception.
就试试吧
Just try it.
我不想浪费电池
I don't want to waste batteries.
我没说让你一天都开着
I'm not asking to keep it on.
我们还是被山挡着
We're blocked by the mountain.
就试一下该死的无线电
Check the damn radio!
如果我试一下  到用的时候我们可能就...
We might not have any juice left when we get to...
天
Oh, my God.
什么鬼东西
What the hell's that?
有东西来了
Something's coming.
我看是向咱们来的
Coming towards us.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's move.
我不该来的
I shouldn't have come on this hike!
Sawyer
Sawyer!
别管他
Let him go!
那是...
That's...
那是一只大熊
That's a big bear.
会是它杀了机长吗
You think that's what killed the pilot?
不是
No.
不  它和那东西相比就是小巫见大巫了
No, that's a tiny, teeny version compared to that.
伙计们  这不光是一只熊
Guys, this isn't just a bear.
还是一只北极熊
It's a polar bear.
你确定他昏过去了吗
You sure he's out?
你怎么知道你拔出来那东西的时候他不会醒
How do you know he won't wake up when you yank that thing out?
我不知道
I don't.
嗨 伙计 你醒了没
Hey, guy, you awake?
看那  救援飞机来啦  我们得救啦  好唉
Yo! There's a rescue plane! We're saved! Yay!
恩  他昏了
Yeah, he's out.
那你想让我...
So, what do you want me...?
他不太可能会恢复意识
It's unlikely he'll regain consciousness,
但可能他会因疼痛而醒来
but the pain might bring him around.
如果这样  你就要按住他
If it does, hold him down.
我不太善于和血打交道哦  哥们儿
Uh... I'm not so good around blood, man.
那就别看
Then don't look.
恩  可是...
Yeah. But...
我不太善于和血打交道哦
I'm not so good around blood.
尽全力好了  好吗
Just do the best you can, okay?
别看
Don't look.
好
Okay.
老兄
Dude.
把止血带给我
Hand me those strips.
老兄
Dude.
把止血带给我  我要把血止住
Just hand me the strips. I need to get this bleeding stopped.
我看我做不来
I don't think I can.
怎么  怎么回事
What? What's going on?
把止血带给我
Just hand me the strips.
给我
Give it to me.
想都别想  Hurley
Don't even think about it.
想都别想 Hurley
Don't even think it. Hurley, hey!
该死
Damn it.
不会是北极熊吧
That can't be a polar bear.
是北极熊
It's a polar bear.
等一下
Wait a minute.
北极熊可不是住在丛林里的
Polar bears don't live in the jungle.
说的就是
Spot-on.
不  北极熊不会住在这么远的南部
No. Polar bears don't live this far south.
这只就是
This one does.
曾经是  曾经
Did. It did.
那东西哪来的
Where did that come from?
可能是熊村吧  我怎么会知道
Probably Bear Village. How the hell do I know?
不是熊  是枪
Not the bear, the gun.
在一具尸体上找到的
I got it off one of the bodies.
一具尸体
One of the bodies?
对  一具尸体
Yeah, one of the bodies.
飞机上不允许带枪
People don't carry guns on planes.
美国执行官就可以带啊  美人儿
They do if they're a U.S. Marshal, sweet cheeks.
飞机上就有一把
There was one on the plane.
我看到一个脚踝有配枪的人躺在那儿
I saw a guy lying there with an ankle holster,
所以我就拿了枪
so I took the gun,
想也许用得着
thought it might come in handy.
看看怎么样
Guess what,
我刚干掉一只熊
I just shot a bear.
那你怎么知道他是执行官
So why do you think he's a marshal?
因为他有一个别针别住的警章
Because he had a clip-on badge!
我也拿了  觉得很酷
I took that too. Thought it was cool.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
你是犯人
You're the prisoner.
你在美国执行官身上找到了一把枪
You found a gun on a U.S. marshal?
恩  我相信是那样
Yes, I think you did.
你知道位置  因为他要把你押到美国
You knew where it was because he was bringing you back to the States.
那些手铐是在你身上的
The handcuffs were on you.
所以你才知道有把枪在那儿
That's how you knew.
滚
Piss off!
这才是你本来面目  你个混蛋
That's who you are, you son of a bitch.
咱们互相怀疑
Be as suspicious of me as I am of you.
你是犯人
You are the prisoner.
行  我是罪犯
Fine, I'm the criminal.
你是恐怖分子
You're the terrorist.
我们都可以扮演个角色
We'll all play a part!
你想当什么
Who do you wanna be?
有谁知道怎么用枪吗
Does anybody know how to use a gun?
扣一下扳机就行了
I think you just pull the trigger.
别用枪
Don't use the gun.
我想把它卸开
I want to take it apart.
枪把下有一个钮
There's a button on the grip.
推一下  弹夹就会弹出来
Push that, it will eject the magazine.
枪膛里还有一发子弹
There's still a round in the chamber.
按住那钮  拉枪的上面
Hold the grip, pull the top part of the gun.
我了解你这一类型
I know your type.
我看不是吧
I'm not so sure.
恩  我和你这样的女孩子打过交道
Yeah, I've been with girls like you.
没有女孩子和我一模一样
Not girls exactly like me.
要给您加满吗
Can I get you a refill?
不  不用了  多谢
I'm fine with this, thank you.
先生  您呢  需要些什么吗
You, sir, can I get you anything?
鸡尾酒  汽水
Cocktail, soda?
就咖啡吧  甜心  黑咖啡
Just coffee, sweetheart. Black.
咖啡  好的
Coffee, sure.
你看起来忧心忡忡啊
You look worried.
我要是你也会这样
I'd be worried too, I was you.
但你要乐观点儿  孩子
But you gotta stay positive, kiddo.
还是有机会他们会相信你的故事的
There's always that off-chance that they'll believe your story.
我知道我就相信
I know I sure do.
我不在乎你相不相信
I don't care what you believe.
这倒是真的
Oh, I know that's true.
一向如此
That has always been true.
你真的不再要些果汁吗
You sure you don't want some more juice?
恩  不要了
Yeah, I'm sure.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentleman,
机长已经打开了"安全带"指示灯
the captain has switched on the "fasten seatbelts" sign.
请返回您的座位并系好安全带
Please return to your seats and fasten your seatbelts.
我求你帮个忙
I have one favor to ask.
真的吗
Really?
看来不错
This oughta be good.
我们该继续前进了
We should keep moving.
不
No.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
谁
Who?
现在倒想检查无线电了
Oh, now's a good time to check the radio.
这之前干嘛去了
Not before, but now.
我们的地势高点儿了
We're up higher.
是啊  可不是吗
Yes, we are.
有一个信号格了
Bar. Hey, we've got a bar!
呼救  呼救
Mayday, Mayday!
是什么
What is that?
什么的反馈  什么东西会那么做
From what? What would do that?
不知道
I don't know.
我告诉你是什么东西--
I'll tell you what.
这家伙不是在修无线电
This guy not fixing the radio.
那东西都不好用了
The thing doesn't even work.
不  不  没坏
No. No, no, no, no, it's not broken.
我们发送不了是因为有其他的信号已经在发送了
We can't transmit because something else is already transmitting.
从哪儿传来的
Transmitting from where?
附近的某个地方  信号很强烈
Somewhere close. The signal's strong.
附近的某个地方
Somewhere close?
就是说在这岛上  好极了
On the island? That's great!
也许是其他的幸存者
Maybe it's other survivors.
我们飞机上的吗  他们怎么--
From our plane? How would they...
这是什么样的传输信号
What kind of transmission is it?
也许是卫星电话或无线电信号--
It could be a sat phone, maybe a radio signal.
能听吗
Can we listen to it?
让我先找到频率  等下
Let me get the frequency first. Hold on.
根本没有发射信号
There's no transmission.
闭嘴吧
Shut up!
是救援队  一定是
The rescue party, it has to be.
是法语  说的是法语
French. The French are coming!
听到法语我从没这样高兴过
I've never been so happy to hear the French.
我没学过法语  她在说什么呢
I never took French. What is she saying?
有人懂法语吗
Does anyone speak French?
她懂
She does.
不  我不懂  什么啊
No, I don't. What?
你在说什么啊  你在巴黎住了一年啊
What the hell are you talking about? You spent a year in Paris!
是喝酒  不是学习
Drinking! Not studying!
重复1-7-2-9-4-5-3-1...
Iteration 1-7-2-9-4-5-3-1.
是什么
Okay, what's that?
不
Oh, no, no, no.
电池快没了
Batteries are dying.
我们还有多少时间
How much time do we have?
我听你说过法语  你就听一下
I've heard you speak french. Just listen to this.
听一下
Listen.
你到底懂不懂法语  因为那会很关键
Do you speak French, because that would be nice.
重复1-7-2...
Iteration 1-7-2...
那声音好怪异  是什么呢
That voice is weird. What is that?
快  快
Come on, come on.
它在重复
It's... It's repeating.
她说的对
She's right.
什么
What?
是一个循环
It's a loop. "lteration."
重复  在重复相同的信息
It's repeating the same message.
是一个计数器
It's a counter. Iteration...
下组数字将以5-3-3结束
The next number will end 5-3-3.
...9-4-5-3-3
谁知道他到底在说什么吗
Does anyone know what he's talking about?
是信息重复次数的计数器
It's a running count of the number of times the message has repeated.
大概是30秒一次  就是说...
It's roughly 30 seconds long, so...
多久呢
How long...?
别忘了翻译  老大
Don't forget to carry the one, chief.
她说...
She's saying...
求求你们...
Please.
她说"求你们救我"
She's saying, "Please, help me."
求你们来救我
Please, come get me.
或者不是  你甚至都不懂法语
Or she's not! You don't even speak French!
让她听
Let her!
闭嘴  哥们儿
Shut up! Man
伙计们  电池  电池
Guys, the battery. The battery.
我现在一个人...
I'm alone now.
独自在岛上
I'm... on the island alone.
快来人
Please, someone come.
他们...他们...
The others, they're...
他们都死了
They're dead.
它把他们杀了
It killed them.
它把他们都杀了
It killed them all.
翻译的好
That was good.
16年
Sixteen years.
什么
What?
16年
Sixteen years...
零5个月 那个计数
and 5 months. That's the count.
你到底在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
重复
The iterations.
是一个求救信号
It's a distress call.
求救或呼救
A plea for help. A Mayday.
如果计数正确的话
If the counter's right...
它已经一遍又一遍地播放了16年了
...it's been playing over and over......for 16 years.
还有人被困在这里吗
Someone else was stranded here?
也许有人来救他们
Maybe they came for them.
如果有人来过  为什么还在播放
If someone came, why is it still playing?
伙计们
Guys...
我们这是在哪儿
where are we?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====